<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Roses xAPI Demo</string>
    <string name="app_title">Introduction to Roses xAPI Demo</string>
    <string name="app_activity_iri">http://adlnet.gov/jobaid/roses</string>
    <string name="app_activity_name">Roses Job Aid xAPI Example</string>
    <string name="app_activity_description">Roses Job Aid</string>

    <string name="lrs_endpoint">https://lrs.adlnet.gov/xapi/</string>
    <string name="lrs_user">lou</string>
    <string name="lrs_password">password</string>

    <string name="preferences_screen_title">Create xAPI Actor Account</string>
    <string name="preferences_key">org.adl.roses.preferences</string>
    <string name="preferences_name_key">name</string>
    <string name="preferences_email_key">email</string>
    <string name="preferences_bookmark_key">bookmark</string>
    <string name="preference_send_init">send_init</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="dialog_title">Continue from last bookmark?</string>
    <string name="default_name">Anonymous</string>
    <string name="default_email">anonymous@anon.com</string>
    <string name="read_verb">http://example.com/verbs/read</string>

    <string name="suspend_button">Suspend</string>
    <string name="previous_button">Prev</string>
    <string name="next_button">Next</string>
    <string name="ok_button">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel_button">Cancel</string>

    <string name="title_activity_rose">RoseActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pruning">PruningActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dead_heading">DeadHeadingActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_shearing">ShearingActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hybrids">HybridsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_floristry">FloristryActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_symbolism">SymbolismActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">SettingsActivity</string>

    <string name="retrieve_attempts_error">Could not retrieve attempts from state: </string>
    <string name="retrieve_as_attempt_error">Could not read activity state attempt data: </string>
    <string name="statement_write_error">Write Statement Error: </string>
    <string name="statement_get_error">Get Statement Error: </string>
    <string name="get_as_error">No activity state returned (could not exist yet)</string>
    <string name="write_as_error">Write State Error: </string>
    <string name="updating_as_error">Error with updating activity state: </string>

    <string name="intent_request_code">requestCode</string>
    <string name="intent_slide">slideId</string>
    <string name="intent_actor_name">actorName</string>
    <string name="intent_actor_email">actorEmail</string>
    <string name="intent_attempt">attemptId</string>

    <string name="scorm_profile_activity_state_id">http://adlnet.gov/xapi/profile/scorm/activity-state</string>
    <string name="scorm_profile_attempt_state_id">"http://adlnet.gov/xapi/profile/scorm/attempt-state</string>
    <string name="scorm_profile_activity_type_lesson_id">http://adlnet.gov/expapi/activities/lesson</string>
    <string name="scorm_profile_activity_type_course_id">http://adlnet.gov/expapi/activities/course</string>
    <string name="scorm_profile_activity_type_attempt_id">http://adlnet.gov/expapi/activities/attempt</string>
    <string name="scorm_profile_activity_category_id">http://adlnet.gov/xapi/profile/scorm</string>

    <string name="mod_what_path">/what</string>
    <string name="mod_what_name">What is a Rose?</string>
    <string name="mod_what_description">Roses Job Aid - What is a Rose</string>
    <string name="mod_what_1">A rose is a woody perennial of the genus Rosa, within the family Rosaceae. There are over 100 species and thousands of cultivars.
        They form a group of plants that can be erect shrubs, climbing or trailing with stems that are often armed with sharp prickles.
        Flowers vary in size and shape and are usually large and showy, in colours ranging from white through yellows and reds.
        Most species are native to Asia, with smaller numbers native to Europe, North America, and northwest Africa. Species,
        cultivars and hybrids are all widely grown for their beauty and often are fragrant. Rose plants range in size from compact, miniature roses,
        to climbers that can reach seven meters in height. Different species hybridize easily, and this has been used in the development of the wide
        range of garden roses</string>
    <string name="mod_what_2">The leaves are borne alternately on the stem. In most species they are 5 to 15 centimetres (2.0 to 5.9 in) long, pinnate,
        with (3–) 5–9 (–13) leaflets and basal stipules; the leaflets usually have a serrated margin, and often a few small prickles on the underside
        of the stem. Most roses are deciduous but a few (particularly from South east Asia) are evergreen or nearly so.</string>
    <string name="mod_what_3">While the sharp objects along a rose stem are commonly called "thorns", they are technically prickles — outgrowths of the
        epidermis (the outer layer of tissue of the stem). (True thorns, as produced by e.g. Citrus or Pyracantha, are modified stems,
        which always originate at a node and which have nodes and internodes along the length of the thorn itself.) Rose prickles are typically
        sickle-shaped hooks, which aid the rose in hanging onto other vegetation when growing over it. Some species such as Rosa rugosa and Rosa
        pimpinellifolia have densely packed straight prickles, probably an adaptation to reduce browsing by animals, but also possibly an adaptation
        to trap wind-blown sand and so reduce erosion and protect their roots (both of these species grow naturally on coastal sand dunes).
        Despite the presence of prickles, roses are frequently browsed by deer. A few species of roses have only vestigial prickles that have no points.</string>


    <string name="mod_pruning_path">/pruning</string>
    <string name="mod_pruning_name">Rose Pruning</string>
    <string name="mod_pruning_description">Roses Job Aid - Pruning</string>
    <string name="mod_pruning_1">Rose pruning, sometimes regarded as a horticultural art form, is largely dependent on the type of rose to be pruned,
        the reason for pruning, and the time of year it is at the time of the desired pruning. Most Old Garden Roses of strict European
        heritage (albas, damasks, gallicas, etc.) are shrubs that bloom once yearly, in late spring or early summer, on two-year-old (or older) canes.
        Their pruning requirements are quite minimal because removal of branches will remove next year\'s flower buds. Hence pruning is usually restricted
        to just removing weak and spent branches, plus light trimming (if necessary) to reduce overall size.</string>
    <string name="mod_pruning_2">Modern hybrids, including the hybrid teas, floribundas, grandifloras, modern miniatures, and English roses,
        have a complex genetic background that almost always includes China roses (which are descended from Rosa chinensis). China roses were evergrowing,
        everblooming roses from humid subtropical regions that bloomed constantly on any new vegetative growth produced during the growing season.
        Their modern hybrid descendants exhibit similar habits; unlike Old European Roses, modern hybrids bloom continuously (until stopped by frost)
        on any new canes produced during the growing season. They therefore require pruning back of any spent flowering stem in order to divert the plant\'s
        energy into producing new growth and hence new flowers.</string>
    <string name="mod_pruning_3">Additionally, Modern Hybrids planted in cold winter climates will almost universally require a "hard" annual
        pruning (reducing all canes to 8"–12", about 30 cm in height) in early spring. Again, because of their complex China rose background,
        modern hybrids are typically not as cold hardy as European Old Garden Roses, and low winter temperatures often desiccate or kill exposed canes.
        In spring, if left unpruned, these damaged canes will often die back all the way to the shrub\'s root zone, resulting in a weakened, disfigured plant.
        The annual "hard" pruning of hybrid teas and floribundas is generally done in early spring.</string>


    <string name="mod_deadheading_path">/deadheading</string>
    <string name="mod_deadheading_name">Rose Dead Heading</string>
    <string name="mod_deadheading_description">Roses Job Aid - Dead Heading</string>
    <string name="mod_deadheading_1">This is the practice of removing any spent, faded, withered, or discoloured flowers. The purpose is to encourage the
        plant to focus its energy and resources on forming new shoots and blooms, rather than fruit production. Deadheading may also be performed for
        aesthetic purposes, if spent flowers are unsightly. Any roses such as Rosa glauca or Rosa moyesii that are grown for their decorative hips should
        not be deadheaded.</string>
    <string name="mod_deadheading_2">Snip off dead rose blooms just below the flower. You will want to leave as much of the cane on the plant while the
        structure of the plant is developing. Also, keep as many leaves on as possible, since the plant needs them to grow strong through photosynthesis.</string>
    <string name="mod_deadheading_3">Choose the type of roses you want to encourage. You can prune the roses in certain ways to encourage smaller,
        numerous blooms or larger, less frequent blooms. The stem you prune is proportionate to the size of the bloom. Prune the stem away above the first
        leaf after the bloom, known as a node, if you want to encourage many smaller buds. The new stem will start from the point at which you cut.
        Prune the stem away at a lower points, such as a meeting of 5 leaves or even lower to encourage large blooms. It will take longer for the blooms
        to develop, but they will be more dramatic blooms.</string>


    <string name="mod_shearing_path">/shearing</string>
    <string name="mod_shearing_name">Rose Shearing</string>
    <string name="mod_shearing_description">Roses Job Aid - Shearing</string>
    <string name="mod_shearing_1">Start by cutting out all dead wood and all canes that are diseased or damaged. Any canes that are old and
        striated (showing deep furrows) also need to be removed. Open the bush up by removing all branches that cross through the center. Cut out very thin canes,
        and remove any branches that cross or rub together.Keep the nice green healthy canes. </string>
    <string name="mod_shearing_2">When removing an entire cane, make the cut as flush as you can to the bud union. If you leave a stub, it can die back
        into the bud union allowing entry for disease and pests. You may need to use a tree saw to get the final flush cut. As the center starts to open up,
        remove any leaves or debris to keep insects and diseases at a minimum. </string>
    <string name="mod_shearing_3">Make all cuts above a leaf bud that points towards the outside of the plant. Make all cuts clean. Try not to make any ragged
        cuts, as this will allow insects and disease into the plant and open it up to infection. Always prune to a healthy bud. Make sure your cut is at a 45
        degree angle going away from the bud. </string>


    <string name="mod_hybrids_path">/hybrids</string>
    <string name="mod_hybrids_name">Rose Hybrids</string>
    <string name="mod_hybrids_description">Roses Job Aid - Hybrids</string>
    <string name="mod_hybrids_1">The favourite rose for much of the history of modern roses, hybrid teas were initially created by hybridising Hybrid Perpetuals
        with Tea roses in the late 19th century. \'La France\', created in 1867, is universally acknowledged as the first indication of a new class of roses.
        Hybrid teas exhibit traits midway between both parents: hardier than the teas but less hardy than the hybrid perpetuals, and more ever-blooming than
        the hybrid perpetuals but less so than the teas. The flowers are well-formed with large, high-centred buds, and each flowering stem typically terminates
        in a single shapely bloom. The shrubs tend to be stiffly upright and sparsely foliaged, which today is often seen as a liability because it makes them
        more difficult to place in the garden or landscape.</string>
    <string name="mod_hybrids_2">The French breeder Joseph Pernet-Ducher initiated the first class of roses to include genes from the old Austrian briar
        rose (Rosa foetida) with his 1900 introduction of \'Soleil d\'Or.\' This resulted in an entirely new colour range for roses: shades of deep yellow,
        apricot, copper, orange, true scarlet, yellow bicolours, lavender, gray, and even brown were now possible. Originally considered a separate class,
        the Pernetianas or Hybrid Foetidas were officially merged into the Hybrid Teas in 1930. The new colour range did much to increase hybrid tea popularity
        in the 20th century, but these colours came at a price: Rosa foetida also passed on a tendency toward disease-susceptibility, scentless blooms,
        and an intolerance of pruning to its descendants.</string>
    <string name="mod_hybrids_3">"Polyantha - Literally \'many-flowered\' roses, from the Greek \'poly\' (many) and \'anthos\' (flower). Originally derived from
        crosses between twoEast Asian species (Rosa chinensis and Rosa multiflora), polyanthas first appeared in France in the late 19th century alongside the
        hybrid teas.They featured short plants—some compact, others spreading in habit—with tiny blooms (2.5 cm or 1 inch in diameter on average) carried in large
        sprays,in the typical rose colours of white, pink and red. Their main claim to fame was their prolific bloom: From spring to fall, a healthy polyantha
        shrubmight be literally covered in flowers, creating a strong colour impact in the landscape. Polyantha roses are still regarded as low-maintenance,
        disease-resistant garden roses today, and remain popular for that reason."</string>


    <string name="mod_styles_path">/styles</string>
    <string name="mod_styles_name">Rose Styles</string>
    <string name="mod_styles_description">Roses Job Aid - Styles</string>
    <string name="mod_styles_1">The wild roses (also known as species roses) include the natural species and some of their immediate hybrid descendents.
        The wild roses commonly grown in gardens include Rosa moschata, the Musk Rose; Rosa banksiae, Lady Banks\' Rose; Rosa pimpinellifolia, the Scots or
        Burnet Rose; Rosa rubiginosa, the Sweetbriar or Eglantine; and Rosa foetida, in varieties \'Austrian Copper\', \'Persian Double\' and \'Harison\'s Yellow\'.
        For most of these, the plants found in cultivation are often selected clones that are propagated vegetatively. Wild roses are low-maintenance
        shrubs in comparison to other garden roses, usually tolerating poor soil and some shade. They generally have only one flush of blooms per year,
        although some species have large hips in the autumn (e.g. Rosa moyesii) or have colourful autumn foliage (e.g. Rosa virginiana)</string>
    <string name="mod_styles_2">An Old Garden Rose is defined as any rose belonging to a class which existed before the introduction of the first Modern Rose,
        La France, in 1867. Alternative terms for this group include heritage and historic roses. In general, Old Garden Roses of European or Mediterranean
        origin are once-blooming woody shrubs, with notably fragrant, double-flowered blooms primarily in shades of white, pink and crimson-red.
        The shrubs\' foliage tends to be highly disease-resistant, and they generally bloom only from canes (stems) which formed in previous years.
        The introduction of China and Tea roses from East Asia around 1800 led to new classes of Old Garden Roses which bloom on new growth, often repeatedly
        from spring to fall.</string>
    <string name="mod_styles_3">Centifolia roses are also known as Cabbage roses, or as Provence roses. They are derived from Rosa x centifolia,
        a hybrid that appeared in the 17th century in the Netherlands, related to damask roses. They are named for their "one hundred" petals;
        they are often called "cabbage" roses due to the globular shape of the flowers. The centifolias are all once-flowering. As a class,
        they are notable for their inclination to produce mutations of various sizes and forms, including moss roses and some of the first miniature
        roses. Examples: \'Centifolia\', \'Paul Ricault\'.</string>


    <string name="mod_symbolism_path">/symbolism</string>
    <string name="mod_symbolism_name">Rose Symbolism</string>
    <string name="mod_symbolism_description">Roses Job Aid - Symbolism</string>
    <string name="mod_symbolism_1">The rose was sacred to a number of goddesses including Isis, whose rose appears in the late classical allegorical novel
        The Golden Ass as "the sweet Rose of reason and virtue" that saves the hero from his bewitched life in the form of a donkey. The ancient Greeks and
        Romans identified the rose with the goddess of love, Aphrodite (Greek name) and Venus (Roman name).In Rome a wild rose would be placed on the door of
        a room where secret or confidential matters were discussed. The phrase sub rosa, or "under the rose", means to keep a secret — derived from this ancient
        Roman practice.</string>
    <string name="mod_symbolism_2">The rose is the national flower of England. The usage dates from the reign of Henry VII who introduced the Tudor rose,
        combining a red rose, representing the House of Lancaster, and a white rose, representing the House of York, as a symbol of unity after the English
        civil wars of the 15th century which, long after, came to be called the Wars of the Roses. The rose thus appears in the histories of William Shakespeare
        and in the Child Ballads. It has been the symbol of England Rugby, and of the Rugby Football Union, since 1871.</string>
    <string name="mod_symbolism_3">In 1986 it was named the floral emblem of the United States, and it is the provincial flower of Alberta (the wild rose) in Canada.
        It is the state flower of four US states: Iowa and North Dakota (R. arkansana), Georgia (R. laevigata), and New York (Rosa generally). Portland,
        Oregon counts "City of Roses" among its nicknames, and holds an annual Rose Festival, as does Pasadena, California, holding the Tournament of Roses Parade
        since 1890 in conjunction with the Rose Bowl since 1902. In April 2011, the United States government space program agency National Aeronautics and Space
        Administration celebrated the Hubble Space Telescope\'s 21st anniversary by releasing an image of spiral galaxies positioned in a rose-like shape.</string>


</resources>
