<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Roses xAPI Demo</string>
    <string name="app_title">Introduction to Roses xAPI Demo</string>
    <string name="app_activity_iri">http://adlnet.gov/jobaid/roses</string>

    <string name="lrs_endpoint">https://lrs.adlnet.gov/xapi/</string>
    <string name="lrs_user">lou</string>
    <string name="lrs_password">password</string>

    <string name="preferences_screen_title">Create xAPI Actor Account</string>
    <string name="preferences_key">org.adl.roses.preferences</string>
    <string name="preferences_name_key">name</string>
    <string name="preferences_email_key">email</string>
    <string name="preferences_bookmark_key">bookmark</string>
    <string name="preference_send_init">send_init</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="suspend_button">Suspend</string>

    <string name="title_activity_rose">RoseActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pruning">PruningActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dead_heading">DeadHeadingActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_shearing">ShearingActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hybrids">HybridsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_floristry">FloristryActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_symbolism">SymbolismActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">SettingsActivity</string>

    <string name="context_name_desc">Roses Job Aid xAPI Example</string>

    <string name="mod_description_prefix">Roses Job Aid</string>

    <string name="mod_what_path">/what</string>
    <string name="mod_what_name">What is a Rose</string>
    <string name="mod_what_description">Roses Job Aid - What is a Rose</string>
    <string name="mod_what_text">
        A rose is a flowering shrub of the genus Rosa, and the flower of this shrub. There are more than a hundred species of wild roses,
        all from the northern hemisphere and mostly from temperate regions. The species form a group of generally prickly shrubs or climbers,
        and sometimes trailing plants, reaching 2-5 m tall, rarely reaching as high as 20 m by climbing over other plants.\n
        \n
        The name originates from Latin rosa, borrowed through Oscan from colonial Greek in southern Italy: rhodon (Aeolic form: wrodon),
        from Aramaic wurrda, from Assyrian wurtinnu, from Old Iranian *warda (cf. Armenian vard, Avestan warda, Sogdian ward, Parthian wâr).
    </string>

    <string name="mod_pruning_path">/pruning</string>
    <string name="mod_pruning_name">Rose Pruning</string>
    <string name="mod_pruning_description">Roses Job Aid - Pruning</string>
    <string name="mod_pruning_text">
        Pruning in landscaping and gardening is the practice of removing diseased, non-productive,
        or otherwise unwanted portions from a plant. The purpose of pruning is to shape the plant by controlling
        or directing plant growth, to maintain the health of the plant, or to increase the yield or quality of
        flowers and fruits. Proper pruning is as much a skill as it is an art, since badly pruned plants can become
        diseased or grow in undesirable ways.
    </string>

    <string name="mod_deadheading_path">/deadheading</string>
    <string name="mod_deadheading_name">Rose Dead Heading</string>
    <string name="mod_deadheading_description">Roses Job Aid - Dead Heading</string>
    <string name="mod_deadheading_text">
        Dead Heading: A form of pruning used on small to medium flowering shrubs to remove spent flowers.
        This is a common method used on Roses. The practice of \"deadheading\" is also a type of pinch pruning:
        it removes spent flowers before they begin to set seed, to concentrate a plant\'s energy on continued flower
        production, for the current year or the following year, as when lilacs are dead-headed after flowering.
    </string>

    <string name="mod_shearing_path">/shearing</string>
    <string name="mod_shearing_name">Rose Shearing</string>
    <string name="mod_shearing_description">Roses Job Aid - Shearing</string>
    <string name="mod_shearing_text">
        Shearing: A form of pruning employed on hedges or topiary, in which most of the growing points are tipped back,
        to produce artificially dense growth. Shearing in general is a more indiscriminate form of pruning,
        where the plant is simply cut to shape, however plants that have been trained to be sheared generally
        produce buds and on the \"surfaces\" where they are to be sheared. It is commonly performed with hedge trimmers.
    </string>

    <string name="mod_hybrids_path">/hybrids</string>
    <string name="mod_hybrids_name">Rose Hybrids</string>
    <string name="mod_hybrids_description">Roses Job Aid - Hybrids</string>
    <string name="mod_hybrids_text">
        Hybrid Tea is a Cultivar Group of roses, created by cross-breeding two different types of roses.
        Grown one flower to a long stem, they are supported by long, straight and upright stems. Most can be as
        tall as 1.8 metres and are repeat flowering. Each flower can grow to 8-12.5 cm wide. Hybrid Teas are the
        worlds most popular type of rose by choice due to their color and flower form. With their long stems,
        it gives them the advantage, over others, as cut flowers. Most varieties, however, lack fragrance and can
        be difficult to grow in the home garden due to a lack of disease resistance and susceptibility to cold temperatures.
    </string>

    <string name="mod_styles_path">/styles</string>
    <string name="mod_styles_name">Rose Styles</string>
    <string name="mod_styles_description">Roses Job Aid - Styles</string>
    <string name="mod_styles_text_1">
        Ikebana is a Japanese style of
        floral design, noted for its simplicity and purity of lines and colors. Often Ikebana
        designs feature sticks and branches such as willow.
    </string>
    <string name="mod_styles_text_2">
        English Country Garden is traditionally
        an English form of designing, but also includes many popular European influences, such as France
        and Holland. These designs are often done as low mounds, or taller vase arrangements that are all-sided
        (360 degrees). Many florists that follow this design style do not use Baby\'s Breath, Carnations and Leatherleaf.
    </string>
    <string name="mod_styles_text_3">
        High Style is a form of design originating
        from the United States. These designs often include a \'less is more\' motto. Flowers that are popular
        among High Style Florists include many tropical flowers such as Birds of Paradise and Anthuriums,
        and also more popular flowers such as Carnations.
    </string>

    <string name="mod_symbolism_path">/symbolism</string>
    <string name="mod_symbolism_name">Rose Symbolism</string>
    <string name="mod_symbolism_description">Roses Job Aid - Symbolism</string>
    <string name="mod_symbolism_text">
        <![CDATA[
            <b>Blue:</b> mystery, attaining the impossible <br />
            <b>Burgundy:</b> beauty <br />
            <b>Coral or Orange:</b> desire, passion <br />
            <b>Dark Pink:</b> gratitude <br />
            <b>Lavender (violet):</b> love at first sight <br />
            <b>Light Pink:</b> admiration, sympathy <br />
            <b>Pink:</b> grace <br />
            <b>Red:</b> love <br />
            <b>White:</b> innocence, purity, secrecy, reverence and humility <br />
            <b>Yellow:</b> Friendship, dying love or platonic love. In German-speaking countries: jealousy, infidelity.
            ]]>
    </string>

</resources>
